<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="my_Array_TRUTH">
    <item>How did you got laid for the first time..!!?</item>
        <item>Tell us about your first Fantasy..!!</item>
        <item>Name one person whom you love most and hate most..!!</item>
        <item>Tell any 5 achievements of your life..!!</item>
        <item>Mom or GF..!!?</item>
        <item>If you could do one thing you did when you were a child, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What do you like to do when you are alone?</item>
        <item>What do you like to do when you are with your friends?</item>
        <item>What was the name of your first crush?</item>
        <item>How old were you when you had your first crush?</item>
        <item>What is the best time of day for you?</item>
        <item>
            What is your least favorite time of the day?</item>
        <item>If you didn’t have to work, what would you do with all your time?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite possession?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite go-to website?</item>
        <item>What was the best day you ever had?</item>
        <item>What was the worst day you ever had?</item>
        <item>Who is the person you are the most jealous of and why?
           </item>
        <item> How many different languages can you speak and what are they?</item>



    </array>
    <array name="my_Array_DARE">
        <item>Kiss the very left person to you Now..!!</item>
        <item>Strip with atleast one of your weared item..!!</item>
        <item>Act like you are transgender and ask for Money..!!</item>
        <item>Call a girl and ask her out with a pick up line..!!</item>
        <item>15 Push-ups right now..!!</item>
        <item>Initiate your neighbors to help you look for your “missing cat.”
           </item>
        <item> Go outside, get in your car and honk the horn 10 times.
           </item>
        <item> Every time someone begins to talk, interrupt by saying, “hey, ya know what?” Keep it up until your next turn.
           </item>
        <item> Take a walk around the block on all fours and bark like a dog.
            </item>
        <item>Call McDonald’s and ask if they sell whoppers.
           </item>
        <item> Call Burger King and ask if they sell big macs.
           </item>
        <item> Kiss the person to your right on the cheek.
           </item>
        <item>Rub your armpits and then smell your fingers.
           </item>
        <item> Pretend you’re a bird and eat cereal off the floor using only your mouth.
            </item>
        <item>Go up to someone, expose their bare feet, and play “this little piggy went to market” on all their toes.
            .</item>
        <item>Every time someone performs a dare, yell, “a mere flesh wound."</item>




    </array>

</resources>